A Guide to the James Whitcomb Riley Collection
University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library, #7133-o
James Whitcomb Riley Collection 1893-1915
University of Virginia. Library. Special Collections Dept. Alderman Library University of Virginia Charlottesville, Virginia 22903 USA
7133-o
12 items
Administrative Information
Access
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Purchase [1972 May 5] 1972 September 1
Item Listing
- Letters
  - Richard Hovey to James Whitcomb Riley, 1893 Jan 20; ALS, 2 p. w/env
  - Edward Eggleston to James Whitcomb Riley, 1897 Apr 5; ALS, 1 p. w/env
  - George Horton to James Whitcomb Riley, 1897 Sep 9; ALS, 1 p. w/env
  - F. W. Cawein to James Whitcomb Riley, 1897 Nov 25; ALS, 4 p. w/env
  - Madison Cawein to James Whitcomb Riley, 1898 May 10; ALS, 4 p. w/env
  - [Harriette] Hovey to James Whitcomb Riley, 1900 Sep 21; ALS, 3 p. w/env
  - John Hay to James Whitcomb Riley, 1902 Nov 12; ALS, 2 p. w/env
  - Henry Van Dyke to James Whitcomb Riley, 1902 Nov 14; ALS, 2 p. w/env
  - Joaquin Miller to James Whitcomb Riley, encl. 2 clippings, 1903 July 24; ALS, 1 p. w/env
  - Madison Cawein to James Whitcomb Riley, 1904 Dec 1; ALS, 4 p. w/env
  - John Hay to James Whitcomb Riley, 1905 Jan 5; TLS, 1 p. w/env
  - Kim Hubbard to James Whitcomb Riley, [1915] Sep 20; ALS, 1 p. w/env